Contact

huzaifaahmed462@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/huzaifaqadeer-digitalmarketingtrainer (LinkedIn)

www.youtube.com/
@huzaifaqadeer_ (Other)
www.facebook.com/
HuzaifaQadeerDigitalMarketer
(Other)
twitter.com/huzaifaahmed_ha
(Other)

Top Skills

Digital Marketing
Graphic Design
Search Engine Optimization (SEO)

Certifications

The importance of campaign objectives

Marketing & Business Strategy

LinkedIn Marketing Solutions Fundamentals

SEO Foundations

Introduction to Graphic Design

Honors-Awards

Golden Certificate Awarded By Digitaldefynd

Diamond Certification Award

Huzaifa Qadeer

Digital Marketing Trainer at Aptech Metro Star Gate Center | Professional Digital Marketing and Advertisement Expert | Digital Graphic Designer

Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

Summary

Hi! Huzaifa Qadeer here from Karachi, Pakistan. Huzaifa Qadeer is a Certified Digital Marketing Expert and Professional and experienced Digital Marketing Trainer & also provides services as a Digital Marketing Trainer at Different private institutes.

Huzaifa have 01 Year hands-on working experience at Aptech Computer Education (Metro Star Gate Center) as a Digital Marketing Executive.

currently he is working with aptech metro star gate center as a Senior Digital Marketing Trainer.

Also he have 03 Years hands-on working experience with multiple Projects as a freelance Digital Marketing Expert.

During Study I started my Career as a teacher at private Islamic School (Name: Madarsa Khair-ul-Islam) I have 2 years' experience in this school, after two years I moved in another private School as a (Computer Science & mathematics Teacher) in this school I served up to 6 months.

I joined Aptech Computer Education (Metro Star Gate Center) in January 2021 as a Graphic Designer (intern) And after six months promoted as a Marketing Executive at Aptech Computer Education (Metro Star Gate Center).

Currently I have provide my services as a freelance Digital Marketer, Social Media Marketing manger, SEO & SEM, Graphic Designer & Digital Marketing Trainer.

In my student life I have served in versatile positions. Also I do freelancing as a (Digital Marketing Manager, Social Media Marketing Manager, Graphic Designer & video editor).

"Huzaifa Qadeer is a flexible worker & always ready to new tasks. If you need a passionate Digital Marketing Expert OR Professional Digital Marketing Trainer, do tap me."

Experience

Aptech Metro Star Gate
Digital Marketing Trainer
January 2022 - Present (1 year 10 months)

I Join Aptech Metro Star Gate Center as A Digital Marketing Trainer in 2022. At Aptech as a Digital Marketing Trainer I provide brief knowledge about

- Digital Marketing
- Trends of Digital Marketing
- Social Media Marketing
- Search Engine Optimization
- Search Engine Optimization
- How you can start your career as a freelance digital marketer
 Benefits of Doing Digital Marketing in present World and much more brief about marketing and Digital Marketing.

Govt.Monotechnical Institute Malir Computer Science Teacher January 2022 - March 2023 (1 year 3 months)

at Govt Monotechnical Institute my role is computer science teacher and at this institute I teched Following topics

- -Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
- Types of SEO
- How Search engine algorithms work
- What is CMS
- WordPress
- -How to live WordPress site and much more ..

Aptech Pakistan

1 year 1 month

Marketing Executive
July 2021 - January 2022 (7 months)
Karachi, Sindh, Pakistan

As Marketing Executive I handled Aptech Metro Star Gate Center's Social Media accounts

like Facebook, LinkedIn, Instagram and others as a Digital Marketing Professional I analyze social media and digital marketing trends and execute new strategy to enhance Aptech's digital marketing presence Graphic Designer
January 2021 - June 2021 (6 months)

Children Life Academy Computer Science Teacher July 2019 - January 2020 (7 months) Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

Education

Institute of Business Administration

Digital Marketing & SEO, Marketing · (June 2021)

Iqra University (Official)
Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science · (2019 - 2023)